Alphabetical Pamphlet Collection
University of Notre Dame Archives
Alphabetical Pamphlet Collection
1878-1977
ALP
4.6 linear feet
University of Notre Dame Archives Notre Dame, Indiana 46556
Scope and Content
Pamphlets, leaflets, novenas, liturgical booklets, catechisms, pastoral lettters, papal encyclicals, reprints, and miscellaneous issues of periodicals; concerning the history of Catholicism in the United States, Catholic tradition, doctrine, clergy, religious orders, celibacy, Canon Law, Catholic Action, anti- Catholicism, the Bible, the social teaching of the popes, labor unions, scholasticism, immigration; the Second Vatican Council, birth control, saints, the Irish, Catholic missions and missionaries, Catholic education, Fascism, communism, socialism, racism, integration, democracy, international cooperation and peace, disarmament, atomic weapons, war, economics, credit unions, rural life, agriculture, masons, secret societies, atheism, and agnosticism.
Catholic Church--United States--History; Clergy--United States; Celibacy; Monasticism and religious orders; Canon law; Catholic action; Bible; Labor; Trade Unions; Scholasticism; Emigration and Immigration; Vatican Council (2d: 1962-1965); Birth control; Irish; Catholic Church--Missions--United States; Catholic education; Fascism; Communism; Socialism; Racism; Race relations; Democracy; International cooperation; Peace; Disarmament; Nuclear weapons; War; Economics; Credit unions; Rural conditions; Agriculture; Freemasons; Secret societies; Atheism; Agnosticism
Related Material
Catholic Literature for Children Collection
Clergy and religious printed material
Archdiocese of Detroit (Mich.) Collection
Drop File Collection
Francis P. Clark Collection
General Collection
Local History Collection
Reynold Hillenbrand Papers
John A. O'Brien Papers
Gordon Zahn Papers
- Alphabetical Pamphlet Collection: Printed Material, PALP
  - St. Francis de Sales Wise and Loving Counsels / by A. M., PALP 1/01
  - The Mask and the Face / by Adamson, Margot - The Sword of the Spirit, c1941; PALP 1/02
  - Jocism, an account of the Continental Youth Movement - La Jeunesse Ouvriere Chretienne / by Addleshaw, G. W. O., 1939; PALP 1/03
  - God and the Professors / by Adler, Mortimer J., 1944; PALP 1/04
  - Thy Kingdom Come: Enthronement of the Sacred Heart of Jesus - Night Adoration at Home, 1944; PALP 1/05
  - Life in Christ / by Ahern, Barnabas Mary CP, 1962; PALP 1/06
  - Catholic Lay Organizations Function and Structure / by Alter, Karl J., The Most Reverend, PALP 1/07
  - A National Educational Policy - As Seen from a Catholic Viewpoint / by Alter, Karl J., Most Reverend, 1956; PALP 1/08
  - A Program for a Better Social Order / by Alter, Karl J., the Most Reverend, 1944; PALP 1/09
  - Secularized Society a Baccalaureate Sermon / by Alter, Karl J., the Most Reverend, 1937; PALP 1/10; At the 93th Commencement Exercises of the University of Notre Dame
  - State Support for Religious Free Schools - 25 Questions and 25 Answers / by Alter, Karl J., the Most Reverend, c1929; PALP 1/11
  - My Gift to Jesus / by Ambrose, Mary, OP, 1942; PALP 1/12
  - Confession to a Priest / by Anderdon, W. H., the Rev. - International Catholic Truth Society, PALP 1/13
  - What Is the Bible? Is Yours the Right Book? / by Anderdon, W. H., the Rev., PALP 1/14
  - To Live Forever / by Anderson, James R., Rev., 1955; PALP 1/15
  - The Mass for Everyman / by Anderson, James R., Rev., 1954; PALP 1/16
  - Teamwork Does It / by Anderson, James R., Rev., 1952; PALP 1/17
  - This is the YCS, Young Christian Students / by Anderson, James R., Rev., 1956; PALP 1/18
  - The Holy Child Jesus and Saint John Baptist de La Salle - Official Handbook of Archconfraternity of the Divine Child / by Angelus, FSC, 1956; PALP 1/19
  - Saint John Baptist de La Salle / by Angelus, FSC, 1936; PALP 1/20
  - I am a Catholic because I am a Jew / by Angress, Hugh Israelowicz, 1943; PALP 1/21
  - Catholic Answers to Protestant Charges / by Anstruther, G. Elliot, PALP 1/22
  - The Protestant Platform / by Anstruther, G. Elliot, 1916; PALP 1/23
  - The Protestant Platform / by Anstruther, G. Elliot, 1932; PALP 1/24
  - Vain Fears / by Antoni, S, STD, 1923; PALP 1/25
  - Another Baby? / by Apollinaris, OMC, 1933; PALP 1/26
  - What is Corporative Organization? / by Ares, Richard, SJ, and Thomas P. Fay, 1948; PALP 1/27
  - The Advantages of Being a Catholic / by Arnold, Robert, 1955; PALP 1/28
  - Into Thy Hands Compline / by Attwater, Donald TOSD, 1944; PALP 1/29
  - St. Augustine / by Irish Messenger Office, 1930; PALP 1/30
  - Daily Compline / by Avery, Benedict R., OSB, 1952; PALP 1/31
  - How to Use the Missal for the Laity / by E. B., 1934; PALP 1/32
  - The Catholic Church in the Scriptures / by Bagshawe, Archbishop, 1927; PALP 1/33
  - The Glowing Cross - A Miracle Playlet for Easter / by Bain, Ethel, 1931; PALP 1/34
  - Heaven / by Baker, Francis A. CSP, PALP 1/35
  - My Religion / by Baldwin, Henry, PALP 1/36
  - I Wish I Could Believe / by Baldwin, John S., PALP 1/37
  - Mixed Marriages / by Bampfield, G. Rev., PALP 1/38
  - Sergeant Jones and His Talks about Confession / by Bampfield, G. Rev., PALP 1/39
  - Why in Latin? / by Bampfield, G. Rev., PALP 1/40
  - Scouting for Catholics Adding the Supernatural / by Barcelo, Louis C, CSC, 1939; PALP 1/41
  - Parish Credit Unions in Missouri / by Barhorst, Barney, 1929; PALP 1/42
  - No Sacrifice - No Priest - Why Anglican Orders were Condemned / by Barnes, Arthur Stapylton MA, 1933; PALP 1/43
  - Paying our Lawful Debts / by Barry, David, STL, PALP 1/44
  - Amusements - Lawful and Unlawful / by Barry, David, The Very Reverend, PP STL, 1936; PALP 1/45
  - My Neighbour's Character / by Barry, David, Rev. CC, 1932; PALP 1/46; Subject: Gossip
  - Cardinal Newman / by Barry, William Rev. DD, PALP 1/47
  - Thought for Freethinkers / by Barry, William Rev. DD, 1905; PALP 1/48
  - The Religion of the Hebrew Prophets / by Barton, J. M., Rev., 1934; PALP 1/49
  - The Conversion of a Modernist / by de Bavier, Andre, D. Litt, 1926; PALP 1/50
  - Mary and the Protestants - Marian Library Studies / by Bea, Augustine Cardinal, 1961; PALP 1/51
  - Catholic Action and Scouting / by Beckman, Francis J. L. STD, 1936; PALP 1/52
  - Labor's Ascendancy / by Beck, Anthony J., 1918; PALP 1/53
  - Catholicism and the Modern Mind / by De La Bedoyere, Michael, 1933; PALP 1/54
  - the Story of The Old Cathedral / by Behrmann, E. H., Rev., 1949; PALP 1/55; Subject: Church of St. Louis IX of France, St. Louis, Mo.
  - Statues and Pictures in Religion / by Belford, John L. DD, 1927; PALP 1/56
  - The Mystical Body of Christ / by Bellanti, L. E., SJ, 1916; PALP 1/57
  - How we got the Bible / by Belloc, Hilaire, 1934; PALP 1/58
  - The Church and Socialism / by Belloc, Hilaire, 1931; PALP 1/59
  - A New Catechism of Christian Doctrine and Practice / by Bellord, James, DD, 1924; PALP 1/60
  - Religious Education and its Failures / by Bellord, James, DD, 1901; PALP 1/61
  - Italian Catholic Feminine Union / by Benedict XV, Pope, 1919; PALP 1/62
  - Appeals for Peace of Pope Benedict XV and Pope Pius XI / by The Catholic Association for International Peace, 1917-1930; PALP 1/63
  - Encyclical of Pope Benedict XV on 7th Centenary of 3rd Order, 1921; PALP 1/64
  - The Pope and the War / by Pope Benedict XV, c1917; PALP 2/01
  - Saint Benedict the Beloved of God - Man's Powerful Helper in Need / by Benedictine Convent of Perpetual Adoration, 1934; PALP 2/02
  - St. Anthony the Wonder-Worker / by Benedictine Convent of Perpetual Adoration, 1931; PALP 2/03
  - Holy Water in the Christian Home / by Benedictine Convent of Perpetual Adoration, PALP 2/04
  - St. Jude Thaddeus Helper in Desperate Cases / by Benedictine Convent of Perpetual Adoration, 1934; PALP 2/05
  - Magnificence of the Love of God and Perfect Contrition / by Benedictine Convent of Perpetual Adoration, 1934; PALP 2/06
  - The Treasures of the Mass / by Benedictine Convent of Perpetual Adoration, 1939; PALP 2/07
  - Wonders of the Miraculous Crucifix of Limpias, Spain / by Benedictine Convent of Perpetual Adoration, 1928; PALP 2/08
  - The Conversion of England / by Benson, R. H. Monsignor, 1926; PALP 2/09
  - Infallibility and Tradition / by Benson, Monsignor, 1907; PALP 2/10
  - St. Peter in the New Testament and in the Fathers / by Benson, Monsignor, 1931; PALP 2/11
  - Maid of the Sacred Sword - The Life of St. Joan of Arc / by Benz, Francis E. and John S. Gibbons, PALP 2/12
  - Seven Sons of a Saint / by Benz, Francis E. and John S. Gibbons, PALP 2/13
  - Is the Pope a King? An Interpretation of the Vatican-Italian Pact / by Bernardini, Filippo, Very Rev., 1929; PALP 2/14
  - The One and Only Church / by Betowski, Edward M., The Rev, PALP 2/15
  - The True Church its Marks and Attributes / by Betowski, Edward M. Rev., 1938; PALP 2/16
  - Why All Should Go to Mass / by Betowski, Edward M. Rev., 1940; PALP 2/17
  - The Roman Index of Forbidden Books / by Betten, Francis S. SJ, 1935; PALP 2/18
  - Why Must I Have any Religion at all? / by Bevan, J. J., 1933; PALP 2/19
  - A Plan for American Society of Catholic Home Missions to operate in the Rural Sections of the United States / by Howard, W., The Reverend Bishop, 1936; PALP 2/20
  - United in Christ / by Benedictine Convent of Perpetual Adoration, 1954; PALP 2/21
  - Good Friday: A Devotional Explanation of the Liturgy / by Biskupek, A., Rev. SVD, 1952; PALP 2/22
  - Purgatory / by Bitter, F., PP, 1934; PALP 2/23
  - May An american Oppose the Public School? / by Blakely, Paul. L. SJ, 1937; PALP 2/24
  - The Blessed Trinity / by Blount, C. F. SJ Rev, 1929; PALP 2/25
  - The Divinity of Christ Proved from His Miracles / by Blowick, John, V. Rev., 1933; PALP 2/26
  - Bl. Richard Langhorne / by Blundell, Margaret, 1933; PALP 2/27
  - The After Life: the Truth and Some Modern Distortions / by Blyton, W. J., 1933; PALP 2/28
  - Saint Bonaventura the Mind's Road to God / by Boas, George, 1953; PALP 2/29
  - How Much Catholics Pay / by Boehning, Russell M. SJ, 1946; PALP 2/30; Subject: Cost of Catholic Education in State of Washington
  - Confirmation: Gift of the Spirit / by Bohen, Marian, OSU, 1962; PALP 2/31
  - The Popes and Christian Citizenship / by Boland, Francis J., CSC, c1939; PALP 2/32
  - Modern Judaism / by Bonsirven, Joseph, Rev. SJ, 1935; PALP 2/33
  - Youth / by Boston, Archdiocese of - Catholic Youth Organization, 1945; PALP 2/34
  - Religious Perspectives of College Teaching in Economics / by Boulding, Kenneth E., PALP 2/35
  - Pitfalls in Science and History / by Boulger, G. S. FLS FGS, Compiler, 1935; PALP 2/36
  - Pitfalls in Science and History / by Boulger, G. S. FLS FGS, Compiler, 1931; PALP 2/37
  - Re-union with the East / by Bourgeois, Charles, SJ; Countess Bennigsen, 1931; PALP 2/38
  - The Physician / by Bourne, Cardinal, 1918; PALP 2/39
  - The Moral Law / by Bouscaren, T. L. SJ, 1944; PALP 2/40
  - How to Converse With God / by Boutauld M. SJ, PALP 2/41
  - A Simple Catholic Dictionary / by Bowden, Charles Henry, 1935; PALP 2/42
  - The Catholic Nurse and the Dying / by Bowdern, William, 1934; PALP 2/43
  - Problems of Courtship and Marriage / by Bowdern, William S., 1939; PALP 2/44
  - World Trends Toward Christian Unity / by Boyer, Charles SJ, 1953; PALP 2/45
  - Church Unity and Russia / by Braun, Leopold AA, 1957; PALP 2/46
  - The Faith and the Peoples of Russia / by Braun, Leopold AA, 1957; PALP 2/47
  - Religion in Russia A Uncensored Account / by Braun, Leopold AA, 1959; PALP 2/48
  - The Catholic Social Movement in Germany / by Brauer, T., 1932; PALP 2/49
  - Learning How to Pray / by Breitenbeck, G. CSSR, 1959; PALP 2/50
  - The Apostolate of the Liturgy / by Brennan, Robert E., Very Reverend, 1948; PALP 2/51
  - Man a Considertaion of the Union of Body and Soul / by Brennan, Robert Edward OP, 1946; PALP 2/52
  - Back to Christ / by Brenner Henry, 1932; PALP 2/53
  - Visits to Theresa Neumann / by Brennan, Elizabeth Marable LLD, 1936; PALP 2/54
  - Christian Priesthood / by Bridgett, T. E. CSSR, 1924; PALP 2/55
  - A Christian Statesman and Political Philosopher: Donoso Cortes / by Briefs, Goetz, 1938; PALP 2/56
  - Must We all Burn? / by Brielmaier, Sylvester, 1948; PALP 2/57
  - The Christianity Courses / by Briganti, Frank, 1960; PALP 2/58
  - The Liturgy and the Laity / by Brophy, Liam, 1955; PALP 2/59
  - A Message to Catholics / by Browder, Earl, 1938; PALP 2/60
  - Scandal the Sin Nobody Knows / by Brown, Francis F., Monsignor, 1938; PALP 2/61
  - Economic Power in the United States / by Brown, George T., 1937; PALP 2/62
  - God and Ourselves / by Brown, Stephen J. SJ, 1931; PALP 2/63
  - A World-Wide Crusade / by Browne, Henry Rev. SJ, 1925; PALP 2/64
  - The Catholic Matrimonial Courts - The Sacred Roman Rota / by Brovne, M. J. DD DCL, 1928; PALP 2/65; Subject: Divorce
  - Stopping the Leak / by Brownson, Josephine Van Dyke, 1936; PALP 2/66
  - The Work of the Catholic Instruction League / by Central Bureau of the Central Verein, 1936; PALP 2/66
  - Pastoral Letter of Most Rev. Paul Bruchesi - The Church Rights in Regard to Marriage; and on The Recently Voted Law Concerning Cremation / by Bruchesi, Paul, 1901; PALP 2/67
  - How to give Sex Instructions / by Bruckner, P. J. SJ, 1937; PALP 2/68
  - Psychoanalysis / by Bruehl, Charles Rev., PALP 2/69
  - Rights and Freedom Imperiled / by Bruehl, Charles, 1944; PALP 2/70
  - Spiritism Ethics of the Ouija-Board / by Bruehl, Charles, PALP 2/71
  - The Status of Woman / by Bruehl, Charles - St. Charles Seminary, 1951; PALP 2/72
  - Woman's Tasks Today - According to Pope Pius XII / by Bruehl, Charles - St. Charles Seminary, 1946; PALP 2/73
  - What is God Like? / by Bruns, Edgar J., 1962; PALP 2/74
  - Are You in Style? / by Buchanan, Rosemary, PALP 2/75
  - How I Became a Catholic / by Bull, George, PALP 2/76
  - Methodism / by Burbridge, A. SJ, c1932; PALP 2/77
  - Address by Rev. John J. Burke CSP, 1920; PALP 2/78; Subject: National Council of Catholic Men
  - The Fruits of Lent / by Burke, John J. CSP., Compiler, 1920; PALP 2/79
  - Lent in Practice The Spirit of Penance / by Burke, John F. CSP., Right Rev., PALP 2/80
  - Lent Its Meaning and Purpose / by Burke, John J. CSP - Gueranger, Dom, PALP 2/81
  - Our Lady's Month / by Burke, John J. CSP, 1915; PALP 2/82
  - Catholic Civilization and the American Republic / by Burke, Thomas F. CSP, 1925; PALP 2/83
  - The Confessional / by Burke, Tom OP, 1934; PALP 2/84
  - Spiritual America and Catholic Life / by Burke, Thomas CSP, 1925; PALP 2/85
  - The Seven Last Words / by Burns, John F., 1953; PALP 3/01
  - Glorious Martyrdom of the Heroic Defender of Christian Education / by Butchkavitch Rev. MSGR., PALP 3/02
  - Confirmation God's Forgotten Gifts / by Byles, Katherine, 1927; PALP 3/03
  - Religion in the Home for the Pre-School Child / by Byles, Katherine Delmonico, 1938; PALP 3/04
  - The South Catholic Discovers Itself - The Catholic Conference of the South / by Byrne, Francis J., STD, 1940; PALP 3/05
  - Fatima and the Rosary / by Cacella, Joseph Rev., c1948; PALP 3/06
  - IT's Your Mass Too / by Calkins, Hugh OSM, 1940; PALP 3/07
  - A Series of Talks given on the Ford Sunday Evening Hou / by Cameron, W. J., 1935-1936; PALP 3/08
  - A Series of Talks given on the Ford Sunday Evening Hou / by Cameron, W. J., 1936-1937; PALP 3/09
  - The Martyr Monk of Manchester - Blessed Ambrose Barlow, OSB / by Camm, Dom Bede OSB, 1930; PALP 3/10
  - Parish Credit Unions / by Campbell, J. M. Rev., c1928; PALP 3/11
  - Mater et Magistra Christianity and Social Progress / by Encyclical Letter of Pope John XXIII, 1961; PALP 3/12
  - The Catholic Church From Without / by Carey, James A. - Catholic Church Extension Society of the USA, 1913; PALP 3/13
  - On Prayer and Expiation in the Present Distress: Encyclical Caritate Christi Compulsi / by Pope Pius XI, 1936; PALP 3/14
  - Canonical Legislation Concerning Religious / Vatican Printing Office, Rome MCMXIX, PALP 3/15
  - The Neo-Malthusians - The Struggle Over the Nature and Dignity of Man / by Carlin, George P., 1959; PALP 3/16
  - The Mother of Christ / by Carroll, Eamon R., O. Carm., 1962; PALP 3/17
  - The Church and the State Is There Any Conflict? / by Carroll, John P. DD, 1924; PALP 3/18; Subject: The Civil and Religious Allegiance of Catholics - National Catholic Welfare Conference
  - Parochial Schools, 1924; PALP 3/19
  - Answer to the Campaign of Bigotry Launched Against Them / by Carrol, John P. DD, 1924; PALP 3/19
  - Eucharist Quizzes to a Street Preacher / by Carty, Charles M. Rev., 1939; PALP 3/20
  - First Fridays and June Devotions to the Sacred Heart / by Carty, Charles M., 1946; PALP 3/21
  - The Freak Religion / by Carty, Charles M., c1931; PALP 3/22
  - Hell Quizzes to a Street Preacher / by Carty, Charles M., 1939; PALP 3/23
  - Indulgence Quizzes to a Street Preacher / by Carty, Charles M., 1939; PALP 3/24
  - True Church Quizzes to a Street Preacher / by Carty, Charles M., 1939; PALP 3/25
  - Virgin and Idol Worship Quizzes to a Street Preacher / by Carty, Charles M., 1939; PALP 3/26
  - The Liturgy Its Use and Value / by Cary-Elwes, Dom Columba OSB, 1937; PALP 3/27
  - Dodecanesian Letter Published in the American Press / by Casavis, J. N., 1945; PALP 3/28
  - A Catechism of Christian Doctrine No. 2 / by Order of the Third Plenary Council of Baltimore, 1929; PALP 3/29
  - A Catechism of christian Doctrine - Revised Edition of the Baltimore Catechism No. 2 / by Confraternity of Christian Doctrine, 1941; PALP 3/30
  - A Catechism of The Liturgy for Young and Old / by A Religious of the Sacred Heart, 1921; PALP 3/31
  - The Official Revised Baltimore Catechism No. 2 / by Horan, Ellamay, 1945; PALP 3/32
  - Catholic Action What Is It? / by Our Sunday Visitor Press, PALP 3/33
  - Catholic Action A Simple Explanation / by The Liverpool Archdiocesan Board of Catholic Action, 1937; PALP 3/34
  - A Missionary Index of Catholic Americans / by Catholic Students' Mission Crusade, USA, 1946; PALP 3/35
  - The Central Bureau of the Catholic Central Union / by The Central Bureau of the Catholic Central Union, 1960; PALP 3/36
  - The Central Bureau Catholic Central Union of America and National Catholic Women's Union Report for the Year July 1, 1958 to June 30, 1959, 1958-1959; PALP 3/37; Subject: Devoted to Catholic Social Action
  - Report for the Year July 1, 1959 to June 30, 1960, 1959-1960; PALP 3/38
  - The Central Bureau Catholic Central Union of America and National Catholic Women's Union Report for the Year July 1, 1959 to June 30, 1960, 1959-1960; PALP 3/38; Subject: Devoted to Catholic Social Action
  - Report for the Year July 1, 1961 to June 30, 1962 / by The Central Bureau Catholic Central Union of America - National Catholic Women's Union and Catholic Central Youth Union, 1961-1962; PALP 3/39; Subject: Devoted to Catholic Social Action
  - A Declaration of Principles / by Central Bureau of the Catholic Central Union, 1962; PALP 3/40
  - Report for the Year July 1, 1931, to June 30, 1932 / by The Central Bureau Catholic Central Verein of America, 1931-1932; PALP 3/41; Subject: In the Service of Catholic Action
  - Report for the Year July 1, 1930, to June 30, 1931 / by The Central Bureau Catholic Central Verein of America, 1930-1931; PALP 3/42; Subject: In the Service of Catholic Action
  - Report for the Year / by The Central Bureau Catholic Central Verein of America and National Catholic Women's Union, 1947-1958; PALP 3/43; Subject: Devoted to Catholic Social Action
  - The Will for Peace / by Catholic Central Verein of America and National Catholic Women's Union, 1945; PALP 3/44
  - Nationalism and Internationalism - A Christian Interpretation of Basic Principles / by Catholic Central Verein of America and National Catholic Women's Union, 1944; PALP 3/45
  - The Buffalo Meeting - Industrial Conference Reports Season 1934 - 1935 / by Catholic Conference on Industrial Problems, PALP 3/46
  - The Cincinnati Meeting - Industrial Conference Reports Season 1934 - 1935 / by Catholic Conference on Industrial Problems, PALP 3/47
  - A Catholic Statement on Negro Employment / by Catholic Interracial Council, 1942; PALP 3/48
  - A Plea for Peace / by The Catholic Laymen's Association of Georgia, PALP 3/49
  - Catholic Churchmen and Cooperatives / by The Catholic Cooperative Committee - Queen's Work and National Catholic Rural Life Conference, 1944; PALP 3/50
  - 6th Annual Report Catholic Rural Life Conference / by Archdiocese of Saint Louis, 1939; PALP 3/51
  - 10th Annual Report 1943 Catholic Rural Life Conference / by Archdiocese of Saint Louis, PALP 3/52; Subject: Brief Historical Sketch 10th Anniversary 1944
  - The Conversion of St. Augustine / by London Catholic Truth Society, 1933; PALP 3/53
  - The Catholic Market - The Magazine of Catholic Institutions, 1963; PALP 3/54
  - Proceedings of the 39th Annual Convention of the Catholic Union of Missouri - 12th Annual Convention of the Catholic Women's Union, 1931; PALP 3/55
  - Proceedings of the 40th Annual Convention of the Catholic Union of Missouri - 13th Annual Convention of the Catholic Women's Union, 1932; PALP 3/56
  - Proceedings of the 62nd Annual Convention of the Catholic Union of Missouri - 37th Annual Convention of the Catholic Women's Union, 1954; PALP 3/57
  - Proceedings 67th Annual - Catholic Union of Missouri - 42nd Annual Convention National Catholic Women's Union, 1959; PALP 3/58
  - Catholicism and Politics / by The Catholic Laymen's Association of Georgia, PALP 3/59
  - Why Catholics Condemn Communism / by National Catholic Welfare Conference, 1936; PALP 3/60
  - The Relation of Religious Instruction to Education / by Cavanaugh, John CSC DD, 1925; PALP 3/61
  - Galileo and other Alleged Failures of Infallibility / by Chabot, Eugene F. SJ, 1932; PALP 3/62
  - Sister Says / by Charitas, Mary SSND, 1951; PALP 3/63
  - The Divine Lover / by Charles, Pierre Rev SJ E. M. E., 1925; PALP 3/64
  - Prayers Before and After Holy Communion / by Chartrand, Joseph, DD, 1926; PALP 3/65
  - Saint-Sebastien hors les Murs / by Cheramy, H PSS, c1925; PALP 3/66
  - What is the Mass? / by Chery, A. OP; Sheppard, Lancelot C., 1957; PALP 3/67
  - What is the Mass? / by Chery, H. OP, 1951; PALP 3/68
  - Divine Mercy in the Doctrine and Prayers of the Church / by Chrosciechowski, Julian MIC Rev., 1960; PALP 3/69
  - National Catholic Youth Council / by Cicognani, Giovanni Amleto, 1941; PALP 3/70
  - Devotion to the Immaculate Heart of Mary / by The Claretian Fathers, 1944; PALP 3/71
  - One in Mind in Heart in Affections / by Clark, William R. OP, 1954; PALP 4/01; Discussions in Preparation for Marriage
  - A Quiet Hour Catechism / by Clark, Francis E. Rev., PALP 4/02
  - The Little Herald of the Enthronement / by Clarke, John P, 1930; PALP 4/03
  - Charity / by Clarke, Richard F. SJ, 1951; PALP 4/04
  - The Existence of God / by Clarke, R. F. SJ, 1932; PALP 4/05
  - Humility 30 Short Meditations / by Clarke, R. F. SJ, 1953; PALP 4/06
  - A Little Book for Holy Week: Meditations and Readings from Palm Sunday to Easter / by Clarke, Richard F. SJ, PALP 4/07
  - Stations of the Cross / by Claudel, Paul; Burke, John J., 1927; PALP 4/08
  - Can Pagans be Saved? / by Claverhouse John, 1947; PALP 4/09
  - The Catholic Church and Party Politics / by Cleary, Henry W., DD OBE, 1928; PALP 4/10
  - The Martin Case / by Cleary, Henry W., DD, 1924; PALP 4/11
  - Poisoned Print and Catholic Moral Theology / by Cleary, H. W. DD, 1920; PALP 4/12
  - The State - Religion League / by Cleary, Henry W., 1928; PALP 4/13; Subject: The Catholic Church and Party Politics
  - Free Masonry - Its Origin Aims and Methods / by Clune, Geo., 1925; PALP 4/14
  - America's Debt in Catholics / by Coakley, Thomas F. DD, PALP 4/15
  - Creeds and Dogmas / by Coakley, Thomas F. DD, PALP 4/16
  - Difference between Catholic Church and Protestant Sects / by Coakley, Thomas F. DD, PALP 4/17